Finding Aid for the The Francis Robinson Collection
Special Collections and University Archives
- (The File Description)
  - Theatre (5)
    - The man Who Came to Dinner (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Medea (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - The Miracle (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Noah (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Theatre (6)
    - Passion Play (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Peter Pan (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Playboy of the Western World (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Pygmalion (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Saint Joan (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Show Boat (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Skin of Our Teeth (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Stage Door Canteen (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Student Prince (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Three Sisters (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - The Time of Your Life (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Tobacco Road (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - The Yellow Jacket (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Classical Productions (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Hamlet (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Richard II (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - Romeo and Juliet (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - Shakespeare - Miscellaneous Plays (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Theatre (7)
    - Abbott, George; Anderson, Maxwell (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Barrie, James; Bernstien, Henry (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Behrman, S. N. (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Eliot, T. S. (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Guitry, Sacha (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Guthrie, Tyrone (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Jeffers, Robinson (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Lindsay (Howard) and Crouse (Russell) (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - O'Casey, Sean (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - O'Neill, Eugene (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Shakespeare, William (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Shaw, George Bernard - Biography (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Shaw, George Bernard - Critiques (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Shaw, George Bernard - Love Life (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Shaw, George Bernard -Plays (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Theatre (8)
    - Shaw, George Bernard - Politics (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Shaw, George Bernard - War (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Sherwood, Robert (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Synge, J. M. (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Wells, H. G. (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Wilde, Oscar (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Williams, Tennessee (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Woods, A. H. (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Woollcott, Alexander (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Yeats, William Bulter (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Stage Managers (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Belasco, David (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Carroll, Earl (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Frohman, Daniel (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Goldwyn, Sam (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Hurok, Sol (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - Kaufman, George S. (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Reinhardt, Max (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - Rose, Billy (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - Ziegfeld, Florenz (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - Critics - General Information (Box 122, Folder 21)
    - Critics (Box 122, Folder 22)
    - Atkinson, Brooks (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - Cassidy, Claudia (Box 122, Folder 24)
  - Theatre (9)
    - Gordon, Ruth (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Kerr, Walter (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Rice, Elmer (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Stevens, Ashton (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Winchell, Walter (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Woollcott, Alexamder - Biography (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Woollcott, AlexanIder - Critiques (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Woollcott, Alexaii‘der - "The Town Crier" (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Press Agents - Publicity (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Henderson, Ray (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Maney, Richard (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Robinson, Francis (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Robinson, Francis (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Publicity (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Theatre (10)
    - Art - general information (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Cocteau, Jean (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Freeman, Don (and Hirschfield) (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Picasso, Pablo (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Artists (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Costumes (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Beaton, Cecil (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Stage Design (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Craig, Gordon (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Jones, Robert Edmund (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Milziner, Jo (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Simonson, Lee (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - De Mille, Agnes (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Cohan, George M. (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Ives, Burl (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Lauder, Harry (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Reed, Susan (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Rodgers and Hammerstein (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Romberg, Sigmund (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Musicians (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - Theatre (11)
    - Gue, Jan. 10, 1970; Mar. 28, 1970 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Newsstand Winter, 1941 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - The Mentor, 1924, 1927, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Playbill, Jan. 20, 1958 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - The Players Bulletin, 1950, 1957, 1959, 1962, 1966, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - The Burr McIntosh Monthly, Comedie Francaise (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Theatre Arts, 1941, 1948, 1950, 1955 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Theatre (12)
    - Theatre World, 1952, 1954 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Plays (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Shakespeare Fistivals (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Shakespeare - Folger Library (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - The Complete Works of Shakespeare (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Theatre (13)
    - Education (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Library Theatre Collections (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Movies (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Theatre (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Personalities (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Dance (1)
    - American Ballet Theatre - Critiques (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - American Ballet Theatre - Publicity (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - American Ballet Theatre - Playbills; Commemorative Booklets (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Ballet Caravan (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Ballet de Paris - Playbills (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Ballet de Paris - Clippings; Playbills (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - American Ballet Theatre (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - American Ballet Theatre (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Dance (2)
    - Ballet International - Publicity (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo - Critiques (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo - History (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo - Personalities (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo - Publicity (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo - Playbills (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo - Playbills (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo - Playbills (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Dance (3)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo - Summer Program (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo - Playbills (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo - Commemorative Booklets (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Dance (4)
    - Ballet Theatre - Critiques (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Ballet Theatre - Personalities (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Ballet Theatre - Publicity (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Ballet Theatre - Playbills (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Ballet Theatre - Playbills (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Ballet Theatre - Commemorative Booklets (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Ballet Theatre Commemorative Booklets (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Dance (5)
    - Ballet Theatre - Souvenir Programs; Commemorative Booklets (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Ballet Theatre - Opera de Paris (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Ballets for America - Publicity (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Bolshoi Ballet - Critiques (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Bolshoi Ballet - Publicity (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Bolshoi Ballet - Souvenir Programs (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Bolshoi Ballet - History (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Bolshoi Ballet - Personalities (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Dance (6)
    - Chicago Opera Ballet (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Jaffrey Ballet (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Jooss Ballet (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - London's Festival Ballet (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Large Ballet Companies (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Small Ballet Companies (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Mordkin Ballet (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - New York City Ballet - Critiques (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - New York City Ballet - Personalities (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - New York City Ballet - Publicity (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - New York City Ballet - Playbills (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Dance (7)
    - Royal Danish (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Trudi Schoop - Comic Ballet Troupe (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Sadler's Wells (Royal ) Ballet - Critiques (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Sadler's Wells (Royal ) Ballet - History (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Sadler's Wells (Royal ) Ballet - Personalities (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Dance (8)
    - Sadler's Wells (Royal ) Ballet - Playbills (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Sadler's Wells (Royal ) Ballet - Commemorative Booklets (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Sadler's Wells (Royal ) Ballet - Miscellaneous (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Dance (9)
    - Ballets Russes de Diaghilew, 1909 - 1929 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Performers - Soviet Union (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Performers - Soviet Union (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Pavlevy-Oukrainsky Ballet (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Baronova, Irina (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Danilova, Alexandra (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Fokine, Michel (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Markova, Alicia (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Markova, Dolin (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Massine, Leonide (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Dance (10)
    - Nijinska, Bronislava (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Nijinsky, Vaslav (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Nureyev, Rudolf (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Pavlova, Anna (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Toumanova, Tamara (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Zorma, Vera (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Background Information - Education (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Background Information - Personalities (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Background Information - Misc. (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Art - Chirico, Giorgio (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Art - Dali, Salvador (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Dance (11)
    - Art - Degas (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Gard, Alex (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Art - Picasso, Pablo (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Art - Miscellaneous (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Martha Graham - Personalities (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Martha Graham - Playbills (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Martha Graham - Critiques (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Martha Graham - Publicity (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Martha Graham - Commemorative Booklets (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Sets and Costumes - Bakst, Leon (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Jose Limon and Dance Company (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Moiseyev Dance Company - Critiques (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Moiseyev Dance Company - Publicity (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Moiseyev Dance Company - Playbills (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Sets and Costumes - Miscellaneous (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Dance (12)
    - Ted Shawn Dancers - History (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Ted Shawn Dancers - Personalities (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Ted Shawn Dancers - Publicity (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Ted Shawn Dancers - Critiques (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Ted Shawn Dancers - Souvenir Programs (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Ted Shawn Dancers - Activities (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Jocob's Pillow - Critiques (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Jocob's Pillow - History (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Jocob's Pillow - Publicity (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Jocob's Pillow - Playbills (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Jocob's Pillow - Souvenir Programs (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Dance (13)
    - Ted Shawn' Annual Newsletters, #1-3, 5-9 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Ted Shawn' Annual Newsletters, 10-14 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Ted Shawn' Annual Newsletters, 15-19 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Ted Shawn' Annual Newsletters, 20-24 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Ted Shawn' Annual Newsletters, 25-28 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - The Dithyramb of the Rose by Angelo Sikelianos (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Dance (14)
    - Ballroom Style (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Bolger, Ray (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - De Mille, Agnes (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Duncan, Isadora - Biographies (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Duncan, Isadora - Family and Friends (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Duncan, Isadora - Miscellaneous (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Enters, Angna (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Hawkins, Erick (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Humphrey - Weidman (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Kreutzberg, Harald (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Losch, Tilly (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Performers - Miscellaneous (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Mower, Lucy Banks (Box 141, Folder 13)
    - Mumaw, Barton (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Wigman, Mary (Box 141, Folder 15)
    - Winslow and Fitzsimmons (Box 141, Folder 16)
    - Shawn - St. Denis - Shawn (Box 141, Folder 17)
  - Dance (15)
    - Shawn-St. Denis - 50th Anniversary (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Denishawn (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - St. Denis, Ruth (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Hurok, Sol and Ballet (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Hurok, Sol - Biographical Data (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Hurok, Sol - Publicity (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Dance (16)
    - Publications - Ballet (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Publications - Dance Index (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Dance Perspectives (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Ballet Publications (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Dance (17)
    - Ballet - General (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Ballet - Miscellaneous (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - American Ballet Theatre - Personalities (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Ballet des Champs-Elysees - Playbills (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Ballet des Champs-Elysees - Playbills (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Ballet de Paris - Playbills, Personalities (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo - History, Personalities (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Bolshoi Ballet - History, Personalities (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Kirov Ballet - Personalities (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - New York City Ballet - History (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Sadler's Wells (Royal ) Ballet (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Bolshoi Ballet - Playbills (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Takarazuka Dance Theatre - Commemorative Booklets (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Ballet Performers - Assorted Oversize (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - Vertes (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - Dance (18)
    - Jacottet, Philippe (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Graham, Martha (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Ethnic American Indians (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Jeter, Sarah and Mith Conlie (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Ruth St. Denis, Ted Shawn, Denishawn, Ted Shawn and His Dancers, Florence O'Denishawn (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Ballroom (Mr. & Mrs. Vernon Castle) Ethnic (Balimere, Carmen Amoaya, Jose Greco, Rosarco and Antonio) (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Isadora Duncan (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Parlova, Anna - Miscelleneous (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Pavlowa, Anna - Portrait (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Dance - Misce114neous (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Gramophone Records
  - Theatre
    - Woollecott, Alexander (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Theatre and Movies (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Press Agents (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Arts and Artists (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Freeman, Don (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Costume Design (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Show, Apr. 1964 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Stage, Jan. 1937 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Stage, Aug. 1937 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Stage, Aug. 1938 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Stage, Sep. 1938 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Theatre Magazine (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Stage, Sep. 1938 - K. Cornell's Autobiography, Part 1 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Stage, Oct. 1938 - K. Cornell's Autobiography, Part 2 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Stage, Nov. 1938 - K. Cornell's Autobiography, Part 3 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Stage, Dec. 1938 - K. Cornell's Autobiography, Part 4 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Stage, Jan. 1939 - K. Cornell's Autobiography, Part 5 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Stage, Feb. 1939 - K. Cornell's Autobiography, Part 6 (Box 147, Folder 18)
  - Theatre
    - Playbills - Paramount Pictures (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Astaire, Fred, Tallulah Bankhead (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Barrymore, John and Ethel (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Bernhardt, Sarah (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Books, Louise, Ina Claire, etc. (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Cornell, Katharine (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Press Releases - Walter Alfird and Willard Keef (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Press Releases - Ray Henderson (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Press Releases - Francis Robinson (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Evans, Maurice, John Gielgud, Gargantua, etc. (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Hayes, Helen, Hopkins, Hope, Howard, Miriami, Leslie, etc. (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Theatre
    - Manstield, Richard (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Oliver, Sir Laurence (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Multiple Artists (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Multiple Artists (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Theatre - Productions (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Theatre - Productions - Shakespeare (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Prints - Shakespeare Characters (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Theatre - Companies, National Theatre (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - American Shakespeare Festivals (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Playwriters - Eliot, T. S., Shaw, G. B., and Multiph (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - MET Programs (1890 -1952)
    - Partial Programs, 1890 - 1909/10 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Partial Programs, 1910/11 - 1919/20 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Partial Programs, 1920/21 - 1929/30 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Partial Programs, 1931/32 - 1951/52 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Partial Programs, undated (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - MET Programs (1895 - 1950)
    - MET Opera Gala and Benefit Performances (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1895 - 1903 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1904 - 1908 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1910/11 - 1929/30 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1930/31 - 1935 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1935/36 - 1949/50 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - MET Programs (1947 -1964)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1947 - 1966 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1950/51 - 1953/54 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1959/60 - 1963/64 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - MET Programs (1964/65 - 1971/72)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1964/65 - 1966/67 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1967/68 - 1968/69 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1969/70 - 1971/72 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - MET Programs (1964/65 - 1971/72)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1972/73 - 1973/74 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1975 - 1977 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - MET Opera Programs, 1978 - 1982 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Programs (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - MET Programs
    - Opera Libretti (MET Opera Programs, the early years of 20th Century) (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - MET Opera Programs, the early years of 20th century (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - MET Opera Programs, the early years of 20th century (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - MET Opera Programs, the early years of 20th century (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - MET Opera House
    - MET Opera House - Old (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - MET Opera House - New (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - MET Opera House and Lincoln Center - (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Lincoln Center Publications (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - MET Opera House and Lincoln Center - (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - MET Opera House and Lincoln Center - Budget Estimates; In-House Memos (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - MET Opera House
    - Metropolitan Opera Club (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Ball in the Opera House - Invitations, Tickets, Menus (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Ball in the Opera House - Seating Lists (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Ball in the Opera House- Programs (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - MET Opera House
    - Metropolitan Opera Guild (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Metropolitan Opera Guild Luncheon (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Annals of the Season (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Viennese Opera Ball - Seating Lists, Programs (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - MET Opera House
    - Metropolitan Opera National Council (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Central Opera Service of the Metropolitan Opera National Council (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Opera Studio (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Metropolitan National Company (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - MET Opera House
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Labor Negotiations, 1948 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Labor Negotiations, 1961, clippings (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Labor Negotiations, Press Releases; Announcements; Survey (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Labor Negotiations, 1964 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Labor Negotiations, 1966 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Labor Negotiations with Orchestra, 1964-66 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Labor Negotiations with Orchestra, 1964-66 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Labor Negotiations, 1969 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Labor Negotiations, 1972 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Labor Negotiations, 1975 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Labor Negotiations, 1977 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - MET Associated Artists, Directors, Designers
    - Engles, George (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Fortune T. Gallo (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Hurok, Sol (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Levine, Marks (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Richmond, Aaron (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Wagner, Charles L. (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Zirato, Bruno (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Berman, Eugene (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Corsaro, Frank (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Dexter, John (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Guthrie, Tyrone (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Large, Brian (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Lunt, Alfred (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - Quinffro, Jose (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Visconti, Luchino (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Wagner, Wieland (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Zettirelli (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Anderson, John (Box 161, Folder 18)
    - Cassidy, Claudia (Box 161, Folder 19)
    - Cummings, Craig C. (Box 161, Folder 20)
    - Denies, Herman (Box 161, Folder 21)
    - Downes, Olin (Box 161, Folder 22)
    - Gilman, Lawrance (Box 161, Folder 24)
    - Hanslick, Edward (Box 161, Folder 25)
    - Lang, P. Henry (Box 161, Folder 26)
    - Maxwell, Elsa (Box 161, Folder 27)
    - Shaw, George B. (Box 161, Folder 28)
  - MET Managers and Assistant Managers
    - Belmont, Eleanor Robson (Mrs. August) (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Bliss, Anthony (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Chapin, Schuyler (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Conned, Heinrich (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Cross, Milton (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Cravath, Paul (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Gatti-Casazza, Givlio (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Gentle, Goeran (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Grau, Maurice (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Edward (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - Kahn, Otto (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - Moore, George (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - Sloan, George (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - MET Staff (Box 162, Folder 14)
    - Taplin, Elijah (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - Witherspoon, Herbert (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - Ziegler, Edward (Box 162, Folder 17)
  - MET - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings
    - Undated Clippings (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - 1950 - 1959 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - 1960 - 1964 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - 1965 - 1966 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - 1967 - 1969 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - 1970 - 1973 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - 1974 - 1978 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - 1979 - 1980 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - MET Manager (Rudolff Bing)
    - Rudolf Bing (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Rudolf Bing (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Rudolff Bing (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Rudolff Bing - Autobiography (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Edinburgh Information for Bing Book (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - MET Opera House
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Prospectus, 1928/29 - 1960/61 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Prospectus, 1961/62 - 1973/74 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - White Paper, June 1971 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Annual Reports, 1966-78 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Financial Statements, 1947-1960 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Financial Statements, 1962-1974 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Opera House - Financial Status - Menus, Reports, Press Releases (Box 165, Folder 7)